{
    "subject": "resource/New_Wet_Kojak",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Band",
    "human_readable": "New Wet Kojak is a Band.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9815216064453125,
            "question": "Is New Wet Kojak a musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227492213249207,
            "question": "Who are the members of New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195359945297241,
            "question": "What is New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.883222222328186,
            "question": "What kind of music might New Wet Kojak play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.826296329498291,
            "question": "Where is New Wet Kojak from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7640618681907654,
            "question": "Where can I listen to New Wet Kojak's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7298839092254639,
            "question": "Are there any well-known songs by New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6700103282928467,
            "question": "Do you know of any upcoming concerts by New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6506487727165222,
            "question": "What is the most popular album by New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5374230742454529,
            "question": "Have New Wet Kojak won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=New Wet Kojak is a Band.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4646_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the most popular album by New Wet Kojak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4646_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know of any upcoming concerts by New Wet Kojak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4646_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any well-known songs by New Wet Kojak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4646_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4646_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that New Wet Kojak is indeed a band, with multiple mentions across different files and contexts. The details provided about its members (Scott McCloud and Johnny Temple), albums (New Wet Kojak, Nasty International, Do Things, etc.), and tour dates further solidify this conclusion."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly mention that \"New Wet Kojak\" is a band, with details about its members and their discography."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}